Margarethe Cammermeyer papers, 1963-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Legal Papers., Bulk, 1991-1997.; 1978-2008.
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume III - Historical, Psychological, and Legal Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume IV - Miscellaneous Expert and Servicemember Declarations - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1991. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume IV - Miscellaneous Expert and Servicemember Declarations - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation (Appeal) Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation (Appeal) Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume 5 - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume 5 - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VII - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1997. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VII - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1997. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume V - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994 March - 1994 June. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume V - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994 March - 1994 June. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume VI - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994 July. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume VII - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994 July-1994 December. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume VII - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994 July-1994 December. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume VIII - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1995. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume VIII - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1995. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume IX - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1995 August - 1998 November. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume IX - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1995 August - 1998 November. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Cammermeyer Retirement Records - Hedges and Caldwell., 1998-1999. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Benefit for Cammermeyer Military Justice Fund - Hedges and Caldwell., 1992. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1989-1992. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1989-1992. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Honors - Hedges and Caldwell., 1990s. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Military Records - Hedges and Caldwell., 1990s. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Letters of Support - Hedges and Caldwell., 1991. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Meinhold Stay Pleadings - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Meinhold Stay Pleadings - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition Transcripts, Notes - Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 5)., 1994. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition Transcripts, Notes - Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 5)., 1994. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition Transcripts, Notes - Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (3 of 5)., 1994. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition Transcripts, Notes - Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (4 of 5)., 1994. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition Transcripts, Notes - Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (5 of 5)., 1994. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Cammermeyer Statement - Hedges and Caldwell., 1989. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Conference Transcript - Hedges and Caldwell., 1992. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Producer Documents - Hedges and Caldwell., 1992. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents from Client - Divorce Proceedings - Hedges and Caldwell., 1980-1984. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Documents Produced in Discovery by Department of Justice - Hedges and Caldwell., 1993 August 30. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Cooperating Organizations - Hedges and Caldwell., 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Press Kit - Hedges and Caldwell., 1989-1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military: Meinhold (1 of 3) - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994-1997. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military: Meinhold (2 of 3 - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994-1997. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military: Meinhold (3 of 3) - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994-1997. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Senate Testimony - Hedges and Caldwell., 1993 May 11. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of John P. Otjen - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994 February 16. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Deposition of John P. Otjen - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994 February 16. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Deposition of John P. Otjen - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994 February 17. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Deposition of Admiral Thomas H. Moorer, (Ret.) - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994 February 23. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - (Appeal) Appellants' Brief - Hedges and Caldwell., 1995 June 16. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Cammermeyer/Pruitt Correspondence Volume i - Hedges and Caldwell., 1993-1994. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1989 November 28- 1992 December 18. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1989 November 28- 1992 December 18. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume II - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1993 January 1-1994 January 31. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume II - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1993 January 1-1994 January 31. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume III - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994 February 1-1994 February 28. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume III - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994 February 1-1994 February 28. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume IV - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Correspondence Volume IV - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Clerk's Docket Sheet - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994 July 11. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Discovery I - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1998. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Discovery I - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1998. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume IX - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1999. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Amicus Curiae Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1995 August. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Amicus Curiae Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1995 August. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Supplemental Excerpts of Record Volume II - Hedges and Caldwell., 1994. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 4)., 1994. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 4)., 1994. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (3 of 4)., 1994. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Edwin Dorn - Hedges and Caldwell (4 of 4)., 1994. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Robert L. Maginnis - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Deposition of Robert L. Maginnis - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Summary of Administrative Proceedings - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991 August 23. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Reply Brief for Appellants - Hedges and Caldwell., 1995. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Administrative Hearing Transcripts - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1991 July. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Administrative Hearing Transcripts - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991 July. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Book Information - Freedom to Differ - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991 July. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1992-1994. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume I - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1992-1994. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume II - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume III - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VIII - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1998. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VIII - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1998. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume III - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume III - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume IV - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume IV - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume IX - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1999. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume II (Appeal) - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1995-1997. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume II (Appeal) - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1995-1997. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VI - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Litigation Volume VI - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Slip Opinion - Hedges and Caldwell., 1996 October 7. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Control Group Regulations - Hedges and Caldwell., 1995 August 14. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Press Releases - Hedges and Caldwell., 1992-1993. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 5)., 1995-1997. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 5)., 1995-1997. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (3 of 5)., 1995-1997. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (4 of 5)., 1995-1997. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Briefs - Hedges and Caldwell (5 of 5)., 1995-1997. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military Challenges: Other Decisions - Hedges and Caldwell., 1993-1995. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - United States Department of Labor/Bureau of Labor Statistics - Hedges and Caldwell., 1998 September 17. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Military: Expert Declarations - Hedges and Caldwell., 1993. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Press Clippings - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1991-1995. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Press Clippings - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991-1995. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Brief for Appellee and Support, Excerpts of Record - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 4)., 1995. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Brief for Appellee and Support, Excerpts of Record - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 4)., 1995. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Brief for Appellee and Support, Excerpts of Record - Hedges and Caldwell (3 of 4)., 1995. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Brief for Appellee and Support, Excerpts of Record - Hedges and Caldwell (4 of 4)., 1995. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Board Action - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 2)., 1991-1993. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Board Action - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 2)., 1991-1993. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (1 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (2 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (3 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (4 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (5 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (6 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Annotated Case Documents - Hedges and Caldwell (7 of 7)., 1991-1995. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer v. Cohen - Correspondence., 1997. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Brief for Appellee Margarethe Cammermeyer - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 August 17. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Reply Brief for Appellants - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 September 15. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Appellee Opposition to Appellants' Emergency Motion - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1994 July 1. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Supplemental Excerpts of Record Volume I., 1994 February 3. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Supplemental Excerpts of Record Volume II., 1994 February 3. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: To Cammermeyer from Attorneys., 1993-1995. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Appeal - Money to Pay Attorneys - Correspondence and Briefs., 1997-1999. (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Series 2: Professional Career and Activism., Bulk, 1991-2002.; 1979-2011.
  This series documents Cammermeyer’s professional careers in the military and as nurse, lecturer, radio host, and congressional candidate from 1979 through 2011. It also documents her activism on lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender (LGBT) issues, particularly in fighting discrimination against LGBT people in the military. This series contains copies of her memoir Serving in Silence and its film adaptation, correspondence including letters of support, congressional campaign materials, photographs, writings including speeches and articles concerning LGBT rights, newspaper clippings documenting her court cases, Serving in Silence, and activism, videotapes and audio cassettes from television appearances, interviews, and Senate hearings, awards she received for her LGBT activism and leadership, and other materials relating to her professional life.
  Organization and Arrangement
  The arrangement of this series is primarily chronological. However, videotapes, awards, and some congressional campaign materials have been grouped by material type.
  The videos and audio cassettes contained in this series must be digitized prior to use.
  - Nursing Career: Correspondence, Clippings, Awards., 1979-1995. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (1 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (2 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (3 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (3 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (4 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (5 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (6 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements (7 of 7)., 1991-1993. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support (1 of 2)., 1991-1995.. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support (2 of 2)., 1991-1995. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (1 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (2 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (3 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (4 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (5 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (6 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (7 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (8 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (9 of 9)., 1991-2010. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Awards, Speaking Engagements, Nursing, Public Relations., 1992-1996. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Subject File: Nomination of Dan Coats as Secretary of Defense., 1992-2000. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Serving in Silence Chapter 5: Drafts, Notes, Reference Materials., 1993-1994. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Congressional Campaign., 1993-1995. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (1 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (2 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence(3 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (4 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (5 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (6 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (7 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (8 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (9 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence (10 of 10)., 1994-1995. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Criticism., 1994-1998.. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence, Congressional Campaign., 1994-1998. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Serving in Silence: Promotions, Correspondence, Agreements., 1994-2005. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Awards: Serving in Silence Film., 1995. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence, Congressional Campaign., 1995-1998. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Serving in Silence, Awards., 1995-2003. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Congressional Campaign., 1997-1999. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Congressional Campaign, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations., 1997-1999. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Congressional Campaign, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations, Serving in Silence., 1997-1999. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Campaign: Guest Book., 1998 November 3. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Campaign Materials (1 of 3)., 1998. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Campaign Materials (2 of 3)., 1998. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Campaign Materials (3 of 3)., 1998. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Subject File: Out at Work HBO Documentary., 1998. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Press Coverage, Congressional Campaign., 1998-1999. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Speaking Engagements, Awards., 1998-1999. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Speaking Engagements, Public Relations., 1998-1999. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Congressional Campaign, Public Relations, Publications., 1998-1999. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Personal, Speaking Engagements, Public Relations., 1999-2004. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Interview with and Speaking Engagements involving Fred Phelps, Jr. of Westboro Baptist Church., 2000 September. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Grethe Cammermeyer Show on GAYBC Radio Network (1 of 2)., 2000. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Forward for Out of the Ordinary: Reflections on Growing Up with Gay Parents., 2000. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Public Relations, Speaking Engagements, Personal, GAYBC Radio Network., 2000-2002. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Writing: Speeches, Articles, Activism, Nursing., 2000-2009. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Letters of Support, Speaking Engagements, Activism, Personal, Awards., 2000-2010. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Application for Hospital Commissioner South Whidbey., 2008. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Awards., 2010. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Serving in Silence: Copies of Books, DVD, Videotape, Cassette Tapes., 1994-1996. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Videotapes (6 tapes): Appearances, Speaking Engagements, Military Career., 1992-1995. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes (14 tapes): Appearances, Speaking Engagements, Military Career., 1993-1996. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Videotapes (14 tapes): Appearances, Speaking Engagements, Military Career., 1996-2000. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tape: Grethe and Fred Phelps, Jr.., 1996-2000. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Campaign: T-Shirts., 1998. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Campaign: Buttons, Pens., 1998. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Videotapes (14 tapes): Appearances, Speaking Engagements, Military Career., Undated. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Box 56)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Box 57)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Box 58)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Box 59)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Box 60)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Carton 61)
  - Awards., 1985-2011. (Carton 62)
- Series 3: Personal Papers., Bulk, 1963-1968.; 1963-2012.